[♪ upbeat music playing]
Travis Japan
SUMMER VACATION!! IN THE USA
[train whistle blows]
[in Japanese]
To plan the best summer vacation ever
for the Travis Japan members,
Noel sets out on a transcontinental
railway trip from Los Angeles.
He makes a stop at a station
called Las Vegas along the way.
But this isn't the Las Vegas
of the casinos.
In fact, this one is a quaint little town.
This town, which thrived
during the Old West,
was a post town
where even outlaws visited.
A Victorian-style building erected along
the railroad tracks emerges into view.
[Noel] First, I visited the information
center across from my hotel.
[in English] Hi.
[concierge] Hi.
This is Noel.
-Nice to meet you.
-Good to see you.
-So, uh, could I ask a question?
-Yeah.
[stammers]
What is the building over there?
So, that is
the world-famous Castañeda Hotel.
-[Noel] Castañeda Hotel?
-[concierge] Yeah,
Castañeda Hotel. That was…
It's a world-famous Harvey House.
That was built in 1899,
and it's the original Harvey House.
-[Noel] Oh! Okay.
-[concierge] Yeah.
[Noel] Historical hotel or something?
-Big legacy 'cause of Fred Harvey.
-Okay.
He's the guy that came and he got a deal
with the Santa Fe railroad.
[narrator, in Japanese] Fred Harvey
was a British entrepreneur
who was prominent in America
during the 19th century.
He founded
the world's first restaurant chain.
He opened Harvey House restaurants
along the railroads one after the other,
delighting travelers with
their high-quality meals and services.
-[in English] That's where the painting…
-This is the original one. Um…
[no audible dialogue]
So, this is a… Las Vegas, New Mexico.
It's a nice old railroad town.
The first railroad town,
essentially in New Mexico.
It was a lot of firsts as far as
-modernization, you could say.
-Mm-hmm.
The first big stop.
The first place with a big trolley.
The first place with telephones.
The first place with electricity
in New Mexico.
So, yeah, that's Las Vegas,
-New Mexico for you. Yeah.
-Ah. Thank you so much.
So, uh, is the hotel available today?
[concierge]
Yes, yes. It's a beautiful hotel
-and it's worth it to go check out.
-Okay. I'd like to go there… go there.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
-Thank you so much. Thank you.
-Thank you.
-Thanks so much.
-Have a good day.
-You too.
[concierge] Oh, hi.
How are you today, sir?
Great. I mean, so do you have
any room available today?
Yes, I do believe we do, sir.
Let me grab a key, in fact, if you like.
It's right here.
-Oh, thanks so much.
-Okay, you're very welcome.
I can go ahead and show you the room,
-if you'd like to see it.
-Yes, please.
Could you let me know that…
Could you tell me
the history of this hotel?
Oh, oh, of the hotel itself? Yes,
it was actually built in 1898.
So, it stayed open for about…
To the late 1940s.
So, what happened was it stayed closed
for about 70 years
until it was eventually restored.
It-It-It was closed?
Yes, about… close to 70 years,
-as a matter of fact.
-Oh, 70 years. Oh, okay.
But the great part about this place
is that it's fully restored,
if you'd like to come
take a look at it as well.
-I can give you the history along the way.
-Oh, I wanna see. Yes.
Your room is just off to the left.
Left?
Listen, you may notice
all of the paintings
on the walls and everything.
These were all done
by the owner's wife herself.
Oh, the owner's wife?
-Yes, she… she's an artist herself too.
-Oh.
And yes, and she actually did
all of these glass stained windows
you see above the rooms as well.
Many people… many people love this room.
It is pretty much known as the hare,
which is the rabbit.
And it was modeled after
the actual Castañeda Hotel.
This is the only room in the hotel
that's modeled
after the hotel as it looked.
[Noel] Whoo.
[gasps]
[chuckles]
[whispers, in Japanese] This is amazing.
Whoa.
I love this!
What a view.
[sighs]
[concierge, in English] So first of all,
I'd like to show you our dining room.
This was actually where we would host
most of the events in the 1900s.
And it was during the restoration,
they went ahead and brought
everything back to life, as you can see.
The grand, um, lights and everything too.
We have all the sitting areas
and all the--
[Noel] Is this made in, like, 18th…
[concierge] Oh, it's actually brand new.
So, well, before the restoration took
place, this whole entire ceiling was gone.
-They had to replace the whole ceiling…
-Oh. Uh-huh.
…along with all the new lights
and everything as well.
-Ah. It was so beautiful.
-Yes.
Yes, I'd love to show you
where our bar area is at too.
That's where they used to serve
all the different people
that were military who came off the train
and stopped in at the hotel
during the last war.
And they would get back on the train
after leave, and they…
-Ah, oh.
-[concierge continues indistinctly]
But I'd like to show you our bar area.
-If you'd like to follow me. This way.
-Yes.
I don't know why, but I feel…
It feels nostalgic or something.
-Oh, yes, yes. [chuckles]
-[chuckles]
Well, we had 30 rooms in the room…
whole hotel at first.
We have 16 up there now.
The thing was, in the early days,
they all shared one bathroom
-instead of having their own.
-Really?
Yes, so during the restoration,
we went ahead and put a bathroom
in each of the rooms.
-Not only that, we extended the size.
-Oh, got it.
Yes, of course. Yeah, and not only that,
they also spent a lot of time
doing the floor.
And this is actually the original flooring
from whenever it was first built.
-Wow.
-[chuckles] Yeah.
[Noel] This kind of, what, 130 years old?
[concierge]
Yes, definitely, definitely, yeah.
The owner definitely wanted
to keep the original flooring,
'cause it adds to the charm
of the building as well.
And just ahead, you can see our bar area.
-We have this place fully redone…
-Oh.
…as well too.
So, these were all local, done locally,
by artisans of the area.
And they came together
and they brought back the entire bar area,
and our mural scene
-you can see right above there.
-Mmm.
That was actually uncovered
during the whole restoration.
-Wow, really?
-Yes.
[narrator, in Japanese]
The Spaniards, Mexicans, the Natives,
and the colonists are depicted
side-by-side on this mural scene.
Painted by a Mexican artist,
this mural represents the deep and rich
history of the American Southwest.
Whoa.
[in English] Looks so cool.
[in Japanese] When they hear "Las Vegas,"
they must imagine the glittering city
that never sleeps.
But this Las Vegas tells a different tale.
The America they've yet to discover.
The Las Vegas they've never heard of.
On this summer vacation trip,
I want the members to discover
the America they've never seen before.
[Shime, chuckling]
This isn't the Vegas I know.
-We made it!
-[Genta grunts]
-[Machu chuckling]
-We made it. We're here.
Isn't Las Vegas supposed to be
the dazzling city with neon signs?
There's, like, nothing here.
-No shops, no people. No nothing.
-Really?
I'd even go so far as to say
that all the stores are closed.
-They definitely are.
-[chuckles]
[Genta] Wait, did we really
come to the right place?
-[Machu] What?
-[Genta] This is where Noel chose.
-That's true.
-It's in his itinerary.
-Well, true.
-So we didn't take a wrong turn.
-We're not here by mistake.
-Right. This must be it. But…
[Machu] We literally just got here, and…
[Genta] Wait, this city feels deserted.
I'm starting to get spooked.
-There's seriously no one out.
-And the lightning along the way… This is…
Did we step into a thriller movie,
or something?
Wait, what time is it?
I know the movie you mean.
The one where the protagonist
-wakes up to a deserted world.
-Yeah. Wait, is this really it?
-It's barely 9:30 p.m. 9:30!
-What are we supposed to do?
Huh? I mean, it's barely 9:30 p.m.,
-and no one's out enjoying the night.
-Is it game over?
-[Machu laughs]
-Day one, and it's game over.
Um, why don't we check
into our hotel, to start?
-[Machu] Good idea.
-[Shime] Let's go.
[thunder rumbling]
[all] Whoa… Whoa. Huh.
-[in English] Hi. Hello. Hi.
-Hi. Hello. Nice to meet you.
-Can we check in?
-[concierge] Check in?
Is here Las Vegas?
Yes, yes. It is.
Well, see the thing about this…
Well, this town is… A lot of people
don't really know it,
but it has a lot more history to it.
Billy the Kid… [chuckles]
[in Japanese]
See, this place is called Las Vegas.
-Yeah. It must be "the first Las Vegas."
-Yeah.
-The first Las Vegas.
-Right. What you'd call…
-It's starting to click.
-This isn't the Vegas… Y'know…
Well, the city we all thought of
is Las Vegas,
-but this is also called Las Vegas.
-Las Vegas.
Right, yes.
So this Las Vegas must be
rich in history and tradition.
Yeah.
-Well… Yes, I guess.
-It's that sort of place.
Yes.
[Machu, in English] Thank you.
[Shime] Thank you.
[Genta, Machu] Wow.
[concierge] Please sit.
-Thank you. Thank you.
-Appreciate it. Thank you.
-We have these two…
-Right. I'll take it.
[narrator, in Japanese] The members,
who aren't quite up to speed
with the situation,
decide to start the night by enjoying
some cuisine that's a local favorite.
[Machu] Whoa. This is awesome.
-This feels historical.
-[Shime] Right?
Well, this is…
This place is so traditional.
Well, yeah.
Wow.
-Oh.
-Oh, oh, oh.
[narrator] They are served enchiladas,
a Mexican dish.
This dish has been enjoyed
by the people of this region
far before the United States
was established.
-[Machu] Thank you.
-[Shime] Thank you so much.
-[Genta] Wow. Thanks so much.
-[Shime] Thank you.
-So I guess the real question is…
-Thank you so much.
…would you like red, green or Christmas?
-[Machu] "Red, green or Christmas"?
-[Genta] Wha-- What… What is that?
-So…
-What is…
[concierge] Red chili is what, you know,
is most well known to go
with our enchiladas with beef.
But green is more well known
to go with chicken.
But Christmas is, well,
most well known in New Mexico
-as red chili and green chili together.
-Oh.
-Both.
-Red and green, Christmas?
-Combine the…
-Ah…
So, right here we have red and green.
-[Genta] Ooh, yeah.
-[in Japanese] What if we each pick one?
-Hey, good idea.
-Good eye.
There are three kinds, after all.
[Genta] Yeah.
Which one do you want?
-[in English] Green.
-Green?
[in Japanese] I'll go with… Christmas.
Christmas.
-All right then.
-Then I'll try Red.
-[in English] Got you.
-Thank you.
[concierge] No problem.
And you said green, right?
The way it's mixed together is that, you
know, there's two ways to do enchiladas.
You can either roll them up
or you can layer them out.
[Machu] Mm-hmm.
These are gonna be rolled up
with your choice of meat inside.
And it's also with the chili
inside as well too…
-[Machu] I see.
-…topped with cheese
and your choice of garnish.
[Machu, in Japanese] Time to dig in.
Hold on, what if it's spicy?
-[chuckles]
-[Machu] Green as well… Green also spicy.
[concierge] I actually really enjoy
the green more myself.
-I love it. Delicious.
-[concierge chuckles]
-[Machu, in Japanese] Great.
-Yeah, green is also spicy.
-[Machu] Yeah. The green one's hot!
-Yeah.
Mmm.
Yum.
[Genta] This hits the spot.
You weren't kidding.
The green one's packed with heat!
-[Shime] See?
-[Machu] No joke.
[in English] Yes, I did grow up eating it
as a child, but, you know,
enchiladas have been around
much longer than I've been around.
It actually dates back
to when Native Americans…
Used to actually be a part of,
you know, their cuisine as well too.
And they made it the best. [chuckles]
-Nice.
-[Machu, Shime] Mm-hmm.
I have a question.
What is that picture, uh, painting?
First opened in the early, like, 1900s.
-The exact date is 1898.
-[Genta] Mm-hmm.
This mural was actually painted by
what we think to be
a famous Mexican painter.
And the best part about the mural is,
it's different walks of life
coming together,
and Native American, he's in the middle,
signifying that, you know,
-he was here first.
-[Genta] Uh-huh.
You know, he was here first…
[in Japanese] They're smiling.
-They're all smiling, yeah.
-Right, yes. It depicts a peaceful scene.
[in English] Peaceful.
-Peaceful. Yeah, peaceful, peaceful.
-[concierge] Exactly, yeah.
All walks of life coming together,
which in the early 1900s,
you know, a lot of different people
weren't as nice to each other
as they should have been.
-[Machu] Mmm. Nice.
-[Genta] Nice.
[Shime, in Japanese] Maybe Noel meant
for us to learn more about the US history.
[Genta] Oh. That's a great point.
In that regard,
he chose the most inept three.
-True.
-Seriously.
But, honestly, we've become hooked.
-I agree.
-Yeah, we're somewhat obsessed now.
Coming to a place like this
and learning its culture is one thing,
-but meeting the locals is another.
-Yes.
And then… there's so much
we learn from conversations
-with the people here.
-Yes.
That's the key takeaway from road trips,
you know?
Maybe that's what Noel intended.
-Maybe so.
-All these
-exciting encounters.
-[Shime] hmm.
It's possible he wanted us to enjoy
the serendipitous encounters too.
Yes.
Everyone we've met so far
has been nothing but kind.
-They're extremely kind-hearted.
-They really are.
-They melt my heart.
-Yes, I feel the same way.
I felt that at the jerky shop too.
Everyone has been so hospitable.
-They've all been so welcoming.
-Yes.
-True.
-I agree.
-This is our turning point. Over time…
-From this point on,
let's be on the lookout for experiences
that feel "right" or "on the right path."
Let's do it.
[Noel] Cuisine which long predates
the founding of the United States.
A blended culture with an enduring history
of various groups of people
living in harmony.
I wonder if the United States'
dynamic culture partially stems from
this great mixing of different cultures.
I hope everyone finds
something to take from this trip.
-[staff, in English] Good morning.
-Morning.
Are you checking out?
-Yes, please.
-How was your stay?
Brilliant experience.
-Thanks so much. Yeah.
-Good. I'm glad you enjoyed it.
-So glad to be here.
-Come back and see us sometime.
-Yes, please. I do. [chuckles]
-[chuckles] Okay.
Oh, so can I have a reservation
for three, uh, end of July?
How… For one night?
-For one night, yes. Yeah.
-Okay.
[Noel, in Japanese] To tell you the truth,
this hotel is notorious for being haunted.
-In the end, I didn't see any ghosts…
-[engine starts]
…but I wonder if
any of the other members will.
They're actually all kind of scaredy-cats.
Shall we get going?
So I won't warn them ahead of time.
[♪ ominous music playing]
[♪ music fades]
[in English] Hey.
-Thank you.
-[in Japanese] You got it?
-Thanks.
-[Shime] No worries.
That's some buttery goodness.
-[chuckles] Yum. It's soft and chewy.
-[Shime] Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Mmm.
-Delicious.
-[Genta] This is the life.
This is my ideal morning.
-[Machu] Mine too.
-[Genta] Mine too. Right?
Yeah. Imagine some music
in the background with this.
-[Genta] I'd love that.
-Yeah.
-I wish I could do this every day…
-Yes.
…but I can never get myself
up in time to do this.
It's easy to talk about doing this,
but in reality,
I can't get myself to wake up.
But you wish you did, right?
-I do.
-It's just that you sleep in.
I can't help it.
Oh, and… you know
how Machu slept in my room last night?
He got really scared about
the history of this hotel.
I did.
It's like…
How do I put it?
My fear won over. I opened the door,
and it was so dark in there.
Machu was in the room across from mine.
-Okay.
-And…
I asked him, "Are you scared?"
And he goes, "Yeah, I am."
He didn't enter his room once.
He chucked his bags in my room
and asked if he can sleep in my room.
-The guy slept in my room!
-[laughs]
Does it sleep two? What a waste,
we each had private reservations too.
Here I was,
looking forward to some alone time.
He got scared, grabbed all his bags,
and crammed my room with them.
And listen to this. My room had two beds.
I planned on sleeping in the bed
closest to the living room
since that side had light.
I was scared too.
-It was my room, you know.
-Yeah.
But then Machu wanted to be the one
to sleep on that side of the room!
-[laughing]
-[chuckling] This guy.
-But you were in Gen-chan's room!
-Tell me about it.
-I'm so demanding.
-Yes, you are.
But Machu's shenanigans
made me forget I was scared.
Well, that's good to hear.
Genta's and my room
were on the second floor.
Right.
Yours was the only one on the first floor.
Since you were kind of isolated.
-I started to really fear for you.
-He did.
So I told Shime
I'm sleeping in Genta's room.
I told him my room is empty,
and Shime goes,
-"I'll come sleep over there then."
-[laughs]
That's the story of how Shime
ended up taking my room.
-So that's what happened.
-Right.
I had to carry my luggage
up the stairs to the second floor.
-Right.
-I asked Machu if he can carry
one of my suitcases.
He came down and actually helped,
only to go ahead of me
and hide in random corners.
He's a serious bully. What a brat.
I told him I was seriously spooked too.
I called out to him,
but he wouldn't come out.
[laughs]
Okay.
-Oh, so that's how…
-Now you see.
-…you ended up showering in my room.
-Yeah.
Yeah. I brought my shampoo
and conditioner to Gen-chan's room.
[all laugh]
I love these summer break vibes.
I feel you.
-It's nice.
-Because we're on summer break.
We are.
-Remember, at the airport…
-You're right about that.
…Noel said this is our summer break.
We get a break from work.
I haven't thought about my work
back in Japan since we came.
[Machu] Same.
I'm enjoying the freedom.
I haven't even opened my schedule.
-[Shime] We'll just try to enjoy it.
-Agreed.
-[Machu] Yes, yes.
-It's the best.
[♪ rock music playing]
[narrator, in English] Moab, Utah.
[in Japanese] Meanwhile, Team A
is enjoying lunch at a food truck park,
where they can try foods
from around the world.
Chaka, Umi, and Shizu check out
-the dishes that catch their attention.
-Holy cow. Which should I pick?
[in English] Here is Greek, Turkish
and Lebanese. Three kitchens mix.
Whoa.
Can I get the BBQ plate?
-BBQ plate, of course.
-Yeah.
-And this is your buzzer.
-Yeah, thank you so much.
Thank you, and this is your receipt
-while you wait.
-Yeah, thank you.
Let me get one chicken with vegetables…
fried rice.
-[Umi, in Japanese] This is crazy.
-[beeping]
Is that mine? That's mine!
It's been a while since
I last took my time eating a meal.
[Shizu] Yeah.
-I'm full.
-[Chaka] Honestly,
I don't even know what I'm eating.
[Umi] Is it cheese?
-Cheese and crab meat.
-Yep.
I'm stuffed. My belly's full.
I got through half my food,
then threw in the towel.
[Umi, in English]
We're Japanese boy's band, Travis Japan.
[Chaka] Travis Japan.
-[parent 1] Oh.
-Really nice to meet you.
-[Umi] Hi.
-What's your name?
-[parent 2] …your name?
-Catalina.
-[Umi] Catalina?
-[parent 2] Catalina.
-[Umi] Catalina.
-[Chaka] Catalina.
[parent 1] Come on. She was…
She was very… She was excited
-'cause she was in Tokyo in December.
-[Shizu] Uh-huh.
-[Umi] Oh, really?
-So, she was studying Japanese.
-[speaking Spanish]
-No.
Oh. Konnichiwa.
-Konnichiwa.
-[laughs]
[band members] Whoa.
[in Japanese] She's precious.
[in English] Good Japanese speaker.
-Yeah. She's trying. She's learning.
-[in Japanese] It's good to meet you.
Arigatou.
[Shizu] Arigatou.
-[laughs]
-[Chaka laughs]
[Shizu, in Japanese] How cute.
[in English] Thank you, Travis Japan.
[narrator, in Japanese] The next day,
the trio start driving
at the crack of dawn
toward Arches National Park.
[Chaka] We'll get there around 6:30 a.m.
It's 6:00 a.m. now.
The sun should be up
by the time we arrive.
[Chaka] It might get unbearably hot.
-Approaching the wall of giant rocks.
-My God. What is this,
-Big Thunder Mountain Railroad?
-[Umi chuckles]
[Chaka]
The real Big Thunder Mountain Railroad.
The rocks' layers are striking.
Found it. Day three.
"Arches."
[Umi, clears throat] It's an arch.
-Is this where the park gets its name?
-[Umi] An arch!
So that's why it's called the Arches.
Is this what's waiting for us?
[Umi] Maybe.
Looking forward to it.
Whoa. It's so open out here.
[Chaka] We must be going higher up.
Remember the mountains
we saw along the way?
-We're a bit higher than that now.
-[Shizu] We're at a higher altitude.
It's like we're in the savanna.
-[door opens]
-[Umi] Whoa.
-We're finally here.
-[Chaka] We're here.
[Shizu] We've arrived.
-[Umi] Look, we can see the sun.
-[Shizu] Really?
Sick, it's bright red.
[Chaka] What a sight.
Yes, this place gives off
-an ethereal feel.
-[Shizu] Right?
Should we take some pictures?
-[Umi] Hold on, give me 30 more seconds.
-[Chaka] Wait, the sun is rising.
[Shizu] What?
-[Umi] I figured it out.
-[Shizu] What a gorgeous view.
[Umi] Are we going even closer to the sun?
[Shizu] I think so.
And we're going higher in altitude.
-I love the vast openness out here.
-The roads are properly maintained too.
This is such a pretty park.
[narrator, in English]
Arches National Park, Utah.
[Noel, in Japanese]
At Arches National Park,
there are
over 2,000 naturally formed arches.
Over eons, elements such as water and wind
shaped these
beautiful sculptures of nature.
-[Umi] Is that a deer? Hey, hey!
-[Shizu] What? A deer?
-[Umi] A wild one?
-[Chaka] Freaking huge. It's huge.
-Do you see how big its eyes are? Ah.
-[Umi] There's a fawn too. Oh.
-They're a family.
-[Shizu] How cute.
[Umi] What if there's a landslide?
[Noel] I want the members to enjoy
the majestic sights
they can't see anywhere else.
Look how precarious this is.
[Chaka] We're only allowed
to hike in permitted areas.
-[Umi] Yeah.
-That's how Mt. Fuji is too.
[Shizu] Oh, you're right.
-Do you see…
-[Chaka] Yeah?
…that smooth-looking rock
in the foreground?
-[Chaka] Okay?
-[Umi] Do you think those are people?
-[Chaka] You're right. They're moving.
-[Shizu] Are we going that far?
-[Chaka] I see them moving.
-[Umi] They're people. Whoa.
-[Chaka] All the way out there?
-[Shizu] Amazing.
-That's pretty far from here.
-[Chaka] Aw.
Wait, how many kilometers
is it to get there?
-And how do we reach it?
-Do we keep trudging along on this path?
[Chaka]
Yeah, we have to keep walking downhill.
[Shizu] Whoa. No way.
[Chaka] That's quite a ways away.
Let's keep walking.
[Shizu] It's the only thing we can do.
-[Umi] I wonder what sort of things…
-[Shizu] …Noel has planned for us.
[Umi] Whoa.
[Shizu] This is incredible.
[Chaka] Hup.
[Shizu, in English] Here you go.
-[Umi, in Japanese] Phew.
-[Shizu] Hup.
Phew.
Whoa.
-Look, these are naturally formed stairs.
-We're scaling a steep hill.
-Whoa. This is insane.
-See how steep it is?
This is ridiculous.
This is all one, big rock.
I can't believe all these people
want to hike up this rock.
[clears throat]
They all do it for the beautiful view
waiting up ahead.
You know,
though I've never been to outer space,
it does make me wonder
if this is what it's like out there.
[Shizu] This is insane.
[Chaka]
It's like we're walking towards the sun.
[Shizu] Right?
[Chaka] This is amazing. It feels surreal.
[Shizu] Is this the road to heaven?
-[Umi] It's very steep.
-[Shizu] Whoa.
[Chaka] The breeze is nice.
-Cute marker.
-[shutter clicks]
[Shizu] Think you can stack another rock?
Don't let it topple.
-[sighs]
-[Shizu] Whoa. Mad skills.
Thank you.
[Shizu] I just hope
it doesn't topple over.
I hope people continue stacking the rocks.
[♪ music ends]
-[Umi] The sun…
-[Chaka] Yeah.
-[Shizu] We're almost there.
-[Chaka] Phew.
-We're so close.
-[Shizu pants]
[Shizu] Hup, hup.
-[Chaka] We're so close to the sun.
-[Shizu] Yeah.
Yeah.
[Chaka] Look, it's an arch.
-See the big cave?
-[Shizu] What?
-You're right.
-[Chaka] It's an arch.
[Umi] Phew… [speaks indistinctly]
Whoa. This is scary.
[Shizu, chuckling] You're crazy.
You're climbing there? That's intense.
[Chaka exclaims]
[Shizu] Ah.
[sighs] What a rough hike.
-Whoa.
-We reached the top.
There's a lot of people here.
What a magnificent painting
nature has wrought.
No human could ever replicate this view.
[Shizu] Right?
[♪ gentle music playing]
-[Shizu] Whoa. Incredible. [chuckles]
-[Umi] Whoa. This is amazing.
[Chaka] There's the arch.
That's what we came for.
-It's beautiful.
-It's huge!
This is what we came to see.
-Whoa.
-This is impressive. What a view.
I'm speechless.
It really is an arch!
[Shizu] I'm lost for words.
No wonder everyone hikes to see this.
[Umi] This is what they come for.
[Shizu] Yeah.
Really though.
I have nothing but gratitude for Noel.
Thank you for showing us
this magnificent nature.
[Chaka] No way.
It looks amazing up close too.
-[Shizu] Yeah.
-[Chaka] The arch!
-It's incredible.
-[Shizu] How is it held together?
-[Shizu] This is phenomenal.
-[Chaka] Is it really safe?
Be careful, everyone.
This really is something else.
I can be here all day.
-It looks even more impressive up close.
-[Shizu, Umi] Yeah.
-It's magnificent.
-How in the world is it standing?
-Nature is full of wonder.
-Yeah.
How did it form in the first place?
But this grand view, really…
you can't convey it with a photograph.
-[Shizu] You really can't.
-[Chaka] I'm deeply moved.
[Shizu] You have to see it in person
to understand.
This is incredible.
[shutter clicks]
[Umi] Whoa.
I may have snapped a miracle shot.
This is incredible.
You know?
When will I ever get to see this again?
Look, we're so close to the sun.
Isn't that incredible?
If I reach, I can almost touch the sun.
This is pure bliss.
Isn't it amazing to be alive?
To put it simply.
[gasps] I might cry.
[chuckles]
If I'm not careful,
I might let a tear slip.
That's how much it meant for me
to hike up that hill.
You know, I have my worries.
I've got lots of stressors in life too.
But when I'm surrounded
by the great outdoors,
and when I hiked up that hill
with my own strength…
it made me feel… so small.
-[Umi] I'm scared!
-[Chaka] Careful, careful, careful.
-[Shizu] Whoa. Now that's a cliff.
-[Umi] Amazing.
[Chaka] Hey…
Look, over there. They're filming us.
[Umi] Oh? You're right.
-[Chaka panting]
-[Umi] Whoa. Don't lose your balance.
Witnessing this view
made me a little emotional.
Yeah. This almost feels like a painting.
It's too magnificent to be real.
I'm starting to understand why Noel
-wanted us to come here.
-[Chaka] Yes.
[Shizu] Yeah, yeah.
It makes me think
of the reason we're alive.
This place is vastly different
from the city we're from.
-I can relate.
-There's an energy to this place.
-There's definitely something special…
-And we would've never experienced…
-…to this place, yeah.
-…this feeling if we never came.
We… are aiming to achieve something
great on the global stage, aren't we?
[Umi, Shizu] Yeah.
And I just wonder, if this is part of
what it means to experience the world.
[Shizu] Mm-hmm.
We're seeing landscapes
we'd never see in Japan.
-[zipper opens]
-[Umi] Look what I brought.
[Chaka] What is it?
-Whoa. Ta-da!
-Whoa. You're the best.
It's the ones we bought!
-Are these hot dogs?
-They are.
Whoa. This view and the hot dogs together?
Unbeatable.
Hot dogs.
-Hot dogs… and this.
-What is it?
Thanks.
Appreciate it.
[Shizu] This can't be real.
The view from the summit
is just magnificent.
-This incredible view…
-With hot dogs!
Oh, squirrel.
What? Whoa, whoa.
-[Umi] It's not a mouse. It's a squirrel.
-[Shizu chuckles]
[Chaka] It hopped out of that hole.
-[Shizu] Let's go!
-[Umi] Let's go!
Digging in!
-[Chaka] Arches National Park!
-[Shizu] Bon appétit.
Yum.
[coughs]
Mustard.
It's delish.
-Simply delectable.
-Fantastic.
Yum.
I wonder if anyone else
has eaten hot dogs here.
-[laughs] Bet we're the first ones.
-No one else, right? Just us.
They're looking at us.
Yum.
[Chaka] This place hasn't changed
since the age of the dinosaurs.
[Umi] What if we're approached
to shoot hot dog commercials?
[Shizu laughs] A commercial
for American-style hot dogs?
[shutter clicking]
[Umi] Two… three years before our debut,
we moved to the United States
to train in LA.
Every grocery haul was exciting.
We always bought too much
like we did yesterday.
And some parts of this trip
remind me of the good old times.
When we're in Japan,
we never shop for groceries together
or share a fridge.
It's these little moments that
bring back fond memories.
It's like, we're making fun
and exciting memories together again.
Yeah. We tend to be homebodies
when we're in Tokyo.
Or, work is usually done at a studio,
which means we spend the majority
of our time indoors.
I wonder if Noel chose this national park
for us for those reasons too.
Personally, I'm a big fan of the outdoors.
I'm glad I was able to come.
I'm really grateful for Noel.
I've known Umi and Shizu longer
than the rest of the group members.
We've worked together the longest.
Not only that, we go way back.
Kaito and I were middle schoolers
and Shizuya was a high schooler
when we first met.
On this trip, I got glimpses
of how we used to be.
I was able to bask in the nostalgia.
I was able to savor our friendship
without worrying about time.
At work, we have to switch gears.
That's not to say
we're always stoic at work,
but on this trip, I got to see
the side of them I rarely get to see.
It was… really nice to feel this way,
and I hope this trip becomes
a memory we all cherish.
[♪ upbeat music playing]
[Genta] Where are we headed today?
[Shime] Today? Oh, I know.
Let's consult Noel's itinerary.
[Machu] Here it is.
Ta-da.
"Today, you are visiting Santa Fe,
a city known as America's Gem."
-Santa Fe?
-Yeah.
"These unique buildings are made
with Native American techniques."
-Oh. Whoa.
-They're made of clay.
Ooh, I wonder
if it's the turquoise aesthetics.
-It's possible.
-It's hot.
"Please enjoy America's
beautiful cityscape and fashion."
-[Genta] There!
-[Machu] Man, I'm excited.
Fashion gets me hyped up.
Genta likes Native American aesthetics
and culture.
-Right? Right?
-It's my thing.
[Shime] And he's a fashionista too.
Oh, Machu, camera, camera.
[shutter clicks]
Wait!
The ISO… Gotta adjust for the sun.
-It's very sunny today.
-Yeah.
I hope the weather stays this nice.
Same.
We may get rained on again.
-No kidding. We might get…
-That's true. Yeah.
-…a sudden downpour.
-It's true.
[Genta] Thanks for driving, as always.
-[Machu] Leave it to me.
-[Shime] We're counting on you.
[Machu] Let's go!
-[Genta] Time to get going.
-[Shime] Let's go, let's go.
-[Machu] Hup.
-[Shime] This is exciting.
-[Genta] I'll put your belongings away.
-[Machu] Oh, thanks.
When the shot changes,
I'm suddenly in the back seat?
-[Genta] I bit my tongue.
-[Machu laughing]
[Genta, Shime chuckling]
[Genta] The sky goes on forever!
[Machu] What a vast sky.
-[Shime] It's so open out here.
-[Machu] Yeah.
[Genta] Just the fact the sky
is so blue and vast…
puts me in a good mood.
-[Machu] Isn't this liberating?
-[Genta] Yeah.
[chattering]
[Genta] What a tasty-looking cloud.
Translated by Megumi Hunter